justmugshots.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy : General Support

**What information do we collect?**    
We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may also be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously if you prefer.

 **What do we use your information for?**    
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

Information we gather from you while visiting and interacting with our website will not ever be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **How do we protect your information?**    
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order  
We offer the use of a secure server.  All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted directly to our Payment gateway provider via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  We do not ever store any sensitive information on our servers or in our databases;  it is transmitted directly to our Payment gateway provider and is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers for any reason whatsoever.

 **Do we use cookies?**    
Yes.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**    
No!  
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**    
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**    
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).  We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**    
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline or via any other means.

**Your Consent**    
By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy (this document).  The latest version of this policy can be found online at the following address:
